https://www.bio.uci.edu/privacy-and-legal-notice/

POLICY
The School of Biological Sciences, University of California, Irvine is committed to protecting the privacy and accuracy of your personally identifiable information to the extent possible, subject to provisions of state and federal law. Other than as required by laws that guarantee public access to certain types of information, or in response to subpoenas or other legal instruments that authorize disclosure, personally identifiable information is not disclosed without your consent.
INFORMATION COLLECTION AND USE
Categories of personally identifiable information collected by Web pages managed or maintained by the School of Biological Sciences, University of California, Irvine or by other entities affiliated with the University of California, Irvine, may include: your Internet location (Internet domain and IP address), type of browser and operating system used to access our site, date and time our site was visited, pages visited on our site, search terms used on our search engines, along with information you use to fill out forms such as: name, email address, address, birthday, student ID number, social security number, credit card number and UCINetID. This personally identifiable information is used to respond to user inquiries. Article IX, Section 9 of the California Constitution grants authority to the University of California to maintain this information.
In order to keep you informed of such activities as campus programs, symposia and/or special events, we may use personal information collected from Web pages for the purpose of future communication back to online enrollees. Such e-mail notification will be conducted in conformance with University of California and campus policies implementing anti-spam laws (pdf).
Additionally, the Web server collects, at least temporarily, the following information: Internet Protocol (IP) address of computer being used; Web pages requested; referring Web page; browser used; date and time. This information is collected to monitor your navigation of our Web pages. We may use browser-IP-address information and anonymous-browser history to report information about site accesses and for profiling purposes. This information is generally used to improve Web presentation and utilization. We also may use IP address information for troubleshooting purposes.
These Web pages may use “cookies” in order to deliver Web content specific to individual’s Web navigation interests or to keep track of online transactions.
DISCLOSURE OF COLLECTED INFORMATION
The School of Biological Sciences, University of California, Irvine will not disclose or share, without your consent, personally identifiable information, except for certain explicit circumstances in which disclosure may be required by law. Nor will School of Biological Sciences University of California, Irvine, distribute or sell your personally identifiable information to third-party organizations.
UPDATING PERSONAL INFORMATION
Questions regarding your options to review, modify or delete previously provided personal information should be directed to webmaster@uci.edu.
POLICY CHANGES
This privacy policy has been created and approved by the University of California, Irvine. Any revisions to this privacy policy will be posted at this URL.
LINKS TO OTHER SITES
You may encounter links to Web pages of entities not managed or maintained by University Communications, University of California, Irvine. Those Web pages may have privacy policies that differ from this one. You also may encounter links to Web sites of organizations not directly affiliated with the University of California, Irvine. Please be aware that the University of California, Irvine is not responsible for the information practices of external organizations. We recommend you review the privacy statements of each Web page that collects personal information.
September 22, 2008
